A Finding Aid to the Museum of Craft and Folk Art Records, 1970-2012, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Museum of Craft and Folk Art records
1970-2012
Archives of American Art
Museum of Craft and Folk Art
AAA.musecraf
Archival Resource Key
28.9 Linear feet
12.48 Gigabytes
The Museum of Craft and Folk Art records measure 28.9 linear feet and 12.48 GB and date from 1970 to 2012. The museum was established in 1982 in San Francisco, California and exhibited local and national craft and folk art collections until it closed in 2012. The collection includes administration records, extensive exhibition files, artists' files, museum publications, printed material, video recordings, born digital items, and photographic material.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 6 series.
Missing Title
Series 1: Administration Records, circa 1988-circa 2010 (0.5 linear feet; Box 1, 0.004 GB; ER01-ER02)
Series 2: Exhibition Files, 1976-2012 (22.7 linear feet; Boxes 1-24, 12.14 GB; ER03-ER50)
Series 3: Artists' Files and Video Recordings, 1983-2007 (0.6 linear feet; Box 24)
Series 4: Museum of Craft and Folk Art Publications, 1977-2012 (1.4 linear feet; Boxes 24-25, OV 31-32, 0.003 GB; ER51)
Series 5: Printed Materials and Commercial Video Recordings, 1983-2007 (2.7 linear feet; Boxes 26-28, OV 33-35, 0.050 GB; ER52)
Series 6: Photographic Materials, 1970-2011 (2 linear feet; Boxes 28-30, 0.282 GB; ER53)
Biographical / Historical
The Museum of Craft and Folk Art was established in San Francisco, California by painter and sculptor Gertrud Parker in 1982. The museum was originally located in a house on Balboa Street and then moved to the Fort Mason Center where it operated for over twenty years before relocating to Yerba Buena Lane in 2006.
Notable exhibitions organized or held at the museum include Innerskins/Outerskins: Gut and Fishskin (1987), Who'd A Thought It: Improvisation in African-American Quiltmaking (1987-1988) which was a traveling exhibition, Folk Art of the Soviet Union (1990), MetalSpeaks: The Unexpected (1997), Emblems of Passage: Art of Africa, Oceania, and the Americas (2002), The Art of Gaman: Arts and Crafts From the Japanese Internment Camp 1942-1946 (2006), and Warren MacKenzie: Legacy of an American Potter (2009). The museum also worked with artists on commission and regularly offered public programs, workshops, and educational outreach events for visitors of all ages. They also partnered with the website Etsy on a popular monthly "Craft Bar" series where people could gather, socialize, and create something handmade.
The Museum of Craft and Folk Art closed in December of 2012. The final exhibition was Fiber Futures: Japan's Textile Pioneers.
Conditions Governing Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Contact Reference Services for more information. Use of archival audiovisual recordings with no duplicate access copy requires advance notice.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Museum of Craft and Folk Art records were donated by Jennifer McCabe, former executive director of the museum, in 2014.
Scope and Contents
The Museum of Craft and Folk Art records measure 28.9 linear feet and 12.48 GB and date from 1970 to 2012. The museum was established in 1982 in San Francisco, California and exhibited local and national craft and folk art collections until it closed in 2012. The collection includes administration records, extensive exhibition files, artists' files, museum publications, printed material, video recordings, born digital items, and photographic material.
Administration records include museum bylaws, lists of early exhibitions, education program evaluations, documents related to public programs, and printed materials.
Exhibition files comprise the largest group of materials in the collection. Notable exhibitions documented include Who'd A Thought It: Improvisation in African-American Quiltmaking (1987-1988), MetalSpeaks: The Unexpected (1997), and Warren MacKenzie: Legacy of an American Potter (2009). There are also video recordings and born digital content scattered throughout the series. Though most of the material is related to the MOCFA exhibitions, there are a few files on exhibitions at other galleries and museums. The exhibition files contain a wide variety of correspondence, art inventories, price lists, printed and digital materials, guest registers, photographic materials, and video recordings, electronic discs, videodiscs, and floppy discs. Artists' files are found for a handful of artists, including Bennett Bean, Ralph Fasanella, Bill Graham, Ron Kovatch, Mike Moran, and Salvador V. Ricalde. The files contain primarily video recordings of artist performances and interviews, but also include resumes and inquiries.
Museum of Craft and Folk Art publications consist of exhibition catalogs, newsletters, reports, and announcements. There are several video recordings of events, such as fashion shows, that were held at the museum.
Printed materials and commercial video recordings include an oversize scrapbook, binders of exhibition press clippings, and folders of clippings on various topics, as well as documentaries and news coverage of the museum.
Photographic materials consist of slides, negatives, photographs, transparencies, and a photo album. The images are of artwork, exhibition installations, events, artists, and museum offices and staff.
Photographs; Transparencies; Video recordings; Scrapbooks; Folk art; Handicraft; African American quilts; Interviews; Visitors' books; African American artists; African American quiltmakers; Art museums -- California; MacKenzie, Warren, 1924-2018; Kovatch, Ron; Graham, Bill, 1931-; Fasanella, Ralph; Bean, Bennett, 1941-; Moran, Mike, 1948-
- Administration Records, circa 1988-circa 2010; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Box 1; 0.004 Gigabytes ER01-ER02
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically with the exception of the public programs folders, which are arranged chronologically. The museum often put up 2 shows at the same time, which is why there are 2 exhibition titles for every public program folder.
  Scope and Contents
  Administration records include Museum of Craft and Folk Art bylaws and guidelines, lists of early exhibitions, evaluations for education programs and public programs, and an architectural rendering of the Yerba Buena Lane building. Materials related to public programs consist of announcements, event scheduling documentation, printed and digital material, and questionnaires from program attendees. There are also 2 videocassettes (VHS) of events probably kept on file for reference.
  - Architectural Color Rendering of Yerba Buena Lane Building, Digital Image, 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.004 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER01)
  - Bylaws, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Education Program Evaluations and Feedback, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fiberworks Retrospective Exhibition Proposal, circa 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Identity Guidelines, 2000; Archival Resource Key; 1 Electronic discs (CD) (Transfer not possible.) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - List of Exhibitions, circa 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Public Programs, Archival Resource Key (Box 1)
    - Invite Reminder, Digital Document, 1998; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER02)
    - Earth and Air and Sticks, 1997 March-June; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - MetalSpeaks and Ed Trinkkeller, 1997 August-October; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - British Potters and Bert Marsh, 1998 March-May; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - June Schwarcz and Face to Face, 1998 June-August; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Chanoyu and Tea Ceremony, 1998 August-October; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Christmas Chreche and Pat Hickman, 1998 October-1999 January; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Illumination and Open and Shut Boxes, 1999 January-March; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Art Carpenter and Delights of Brazil, 1999 March-May; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Fiber Eloquence and Pierrot Barra, 1999 June-August; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Reference Material, circa 1985-circa 2000; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videocassettes (VHS) recordings probably used for reference or research, contents uncertain due to vague labels (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Exhibition Files, 1976-2012; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 22.7 Linear feet Boxes 1-24; 12.14 Gigabytes ER03-ER50
  The bulk of this series is comprised of Museum of Craft and Folk Art exhibitions, but there are also a few exhibitions at other art venues. The series includes correspondence, shipping notices, art inventories, price lists, printed materials, guest registers, and photographic materials. Notable exhibitions include Innerskins/Outerskins: Gut and Fishskin (1987), Who'd A Thought It: Improvisation in African-American Quiltmaking (1987-1988) which was a traveling exhibition, Folk Art of the Soviet Union (1990), MetalSpeaks: The Unexpected (1997), Emblems of Passage: Art of Africa, Oceania, and the Americas (2002), The Art of Gaman: Arts and Crafts From the Japanese Internment Camp 1942-1946 (2006), and Warren MacKenzie: Legacy of an American Potter (2009). There are also 46 videocassettes, and born digital materials of exhibition events, artist interviews, performances, and general documentation.
  The exhibitions are arranged chronologically by year, then alphabetically by title within each year.
  - Boats, Trains, Cars & Planes: Folk Art from Many Places (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Camel Belts from the Great Indian Desert (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - June Schwarcz: Enameled Bowls and Wall Pieces (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Katherine Westphal: Papers to Wear (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Mexican Ceremonial Masks (1983), 1976-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Trends and Traditions: Craft and Folk Art from the Bay Area (1983), 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - American Art Pottery, 1890-1950 (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Belts and Fajas of the Americas: Collected by Richard Valentino (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Excessories: Gaza Bowen (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Form and Color: Rudolph Schaeffer Collects for Teaching (1984), 1981-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Little Black Dress (& A Few Aprons, Etc., Etc.): The Power, Function, Ceremony of Black (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Majolica from Faenza (1984), 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Musical Instruments of the Third World (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Native Arts of Luzon: Philippine Traditions (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Rebecca Stephens: Color Xerography (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Ancient Symbols: The Language of Oriental Rugs (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Ann Christenson Sculpture: Ceramic and Steel (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Art in Haitian Vodou (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Shawcroft (1985), 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Design for Living: 1910 (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Kerry Vander Meer "Atlantillian Images" (1985), 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Shelley Jurs: Architectural Glass (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Textiles of Old Japan: Bast Fiber Textiles and Old Kasuri (1985), 1984-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - Art of the Lesser Sunda Islands (1986), 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
  - Heirloom Quilts: The Gaby Burkert Collection (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11-13)
  - Max Pollak: Artist and Collector (1986), 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The Road to Heaven is Built by Good Works: Southern Black Visionaries (1986), 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
  - A Sculptor's Place: J. B. Blunk (1986), Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
  - Textiles of Old Japan: Color and Dye (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Textiles of Old Japan: Color and Dye (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bay Currents: Clay and Glass (1987), 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2-4)
  - Contrasts in Wood: John Abduljaami and Harold Pepperell (1987), 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
  - Enduring Traditions: Tibetan Folk Art (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7-9)
  - From Aid to Art: Decorated Flour Sacks from World War I (1987), 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hopi Art: A Century of Continuity and Change (1987), 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11-14)
  - Innerskins/Outerskins: Gut and Fishskin (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - Artist Information, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Innerskins/Outerskins: Gut and Fishskin (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Artist Information and Condition Reports, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Condition Reports and Shipping, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Loan Forms, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Inventories and Photographic Material, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4-6)
  - Who'd A Thought It: Improvisation in African-American Quiltmaking (1987-1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - General Exhibition Information, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Traveling Exhibition Agreements, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8-11)
    - Condition Reports, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
    - Traveling Exhibition Checklists and Information, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Printed Material and Publicity, 1988-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Photographic Material, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
  - Who'd A Thought It: Improvisation in African-American Quiltmaking (1987-1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
    - Exhibition Recordings, circa 1988; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) Original; 2 Videocassettes (VHS) duplicates (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - News Coverage, circa 1988; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 88 Jewels: National Juried Competition of Contemporary Jewelry (1988), 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
  - Above the Shoulders: Suzanne Benton, Candace King, Adam Kurtzman (1988), 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
  - Clay and Skin Pots by Allen Moe (1988), 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Not So Naive: Bay Area Artists and Outsider Art (1988), 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8-10)
  - Paintings by Folk Artist Alexander Maldonaldo (1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sun and Moon: Traditional Arts of Yi Dynasty Korea (1988), 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - This is Who We Are: Weaving and Costumes from Tarabuco, Bolivia (1988), 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13-14)
  - The Arts and Crafts Studio of Dirk Van Erp (1989), 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
  - Bay Area Violin Bow Makers (1989), 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Dolls as Mirrors of Culture: The Gregory Collection (1989), 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Glass Inventions, Silica Dreams: Three Pacific Northwest Artists (1989), 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Joanne Segal Brandford: Baskets and Nets (1989), 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Life and History of Hog Hammock: Sculptures and Drawings by Aminah Robinson (1989), 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Maritime Arts and Artisans: Collection of the San Francisco Maritime National Historical Park (1989), 1985-1989; Archival Resource Key; Includes born digital records, see ER03. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Masters of Their Material Culture: The Traditions of Nautical arts and Crafts, essay by Robert J. Schwendinger, Digital Document, 1989; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER03)
  - Minority Costumes and Textiles of Guizhou Province, The People's Democratic Republic of China (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - China Correspondence, 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and Exhibition Information, 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition Proposal and Inventory, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Insurance, Sales, Research, and Travel, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Photograph Labels, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Photographic Material, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - News Coverage and Exhibition Recording, circa 1989; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - The Paper Dolls of Satch Valley (1989), 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Adam and Eve Imagery: 20th Century Non-Academic Art (1990), 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13-15)
  - Andean Folk Knitting (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Beyond Words: The Book as Metaphor for Art (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Brian Gladwell: Cardboard Furniture (1990), 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - Folk Art of the Soviet Union (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Object Lists, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Shipping Insurance, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Audio Tours, Association Series, Preview Party, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Publications and Photographic Material, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Tour Information, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Photographs of Art, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "Folk Art of the Soviet Union - Crafts Being Made", 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - In Celebration: The Baskets of Ed Rossbach (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - An Old Turkish House (1990), 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
  - The Painter as Sculptor and Collector: John Haley (1990), 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
  - The Quiet Eye: Pottery of Shoji Hamada and Bernard Leach (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Notebook, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Printed Material, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Photographic Material, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Leach Pottery, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Reiko Brandon: Bridging Two Cultures with Fiber (1990), 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Tramp Art (1990), 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Art on Wheels (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - California Cutlery (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - The California Duck (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Eliminating Definitions: Installations by Four Bay Area Artists (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Katherine Westphal: The Grand Tou r (1991), 1977-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
  - Looking Pretty, Sitting Fine: The Baltimore Screens and Folk Art Chairs (1991), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 8, Folder 14-16)
  - Mythical Figures and Fantastic Facades: Nance O'Banion and Peter Winter (1991), 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - New Metal Work: Judith Hoffman and Bruce Metcalf (1991), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Ogbozo: An Igbo Maskmaker of Nigeria (1991), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Perfection in Porcelain: Armin Muller (1991), 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Indonesian Textiles: Heritage in Cloth (1991-1992), 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Classical Chinese Furniture (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Doris Miller: Raku Vessels (1992), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Julia Morgan: Architecture Rendered Beautiful (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
  - Lillian Elliott: Baskets and Textiles and Lillian Elliott Collects (1992), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Many Mansions: The Art of Shelter (1992), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
  - Tivaivai: Cook Island Quilts (1992), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Hand Bookbinders of California (1992-1993), 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Papercuts (1992-1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
  - Art Deco in San Francisco (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15-17)
  - Beads: Ancient, Traditional, Tribal and Trade (1993), 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Face to Face: Clayton Bailey and Traditional Southern Face Vessels (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - From the Heart of Ogun: Steel Drum Sculptures of Haiti (1993), 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Gertrud Parker: A Lightness in Being (1993), 1988-1993; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videocassette (VHS). (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
  - Jolanta Pachowksa and Son Filip: A Collaboration (1993), 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Madeline De Joly: Libraries of Confluence (1993), 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Memories in the Tips of Our Fingers (1993), 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Nine Decades: The Northern California Craft Movement (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, Condition Reports, Grants, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Labels and Loan Forms, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Research on Artists, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
    - Photographic Material, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Contemporary American Indian Art: Lakota Star Quilts (1993-1994), 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Contemporary American Indian Art: Lakota Star Quilts (1993-1994), 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Unknown Africa: Selections from the Collection of Dan Crowley (1993-1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Con Mucha Alegria: Bolivian Festival Masks and Costumes (1994), 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Contemporary Cast Glass (1994), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Making Sense: Storytelling in Contemporary Bay Area Art (1994), 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Marilyn and Jack Da Silva: Metalsmiths (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)